[
  {
    "_id": "6765a8511e63cbb9c3ad3b1a",
    "courseId": "6762f8b6e8e5ff606e583619",
    "title": "Quiz 1",
    "description": "An MCQ quiz for chapter 1",
    "numOfQuestions": 3,
    "status": "Available",
    "easyQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "What is TCP",
        "options": [
          "A protocol",
          "A suit",
          "A model",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A protocol"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the data at network layer?",
        "options": [
          "Segment",
          "User datagrame",
          "Datagrame",
          "Frame"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Datagrame"
      }
    ],
    "mediumQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following protocols is used for email services?",
        "options": [
          "SMTP",
          "FTP",
          "HTTP",
          "IMAP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "SMTP"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a subnet mask do in a network?",
        "options": [
          "Defines the gateway",
          "Determines the host ID and network ID",
          "Specifies the MAC address",
          "Controls data speed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Determines the host ID and network ID"
      }
    ],
    "hardQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main function of a DNS server?",
        "options": [
          "Routes traffic on a network",
          "Translates domain names to IP addresses",
          "Manages the ARP table",
          "Encrypts HTTP traffic"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Translates domain names to IP addresses"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocol is used for error reporting in IP communication?",
        "options": [
          "ICMP",
          "ARP",
          "RARP",
          "UDP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "ICMP"
      }
    ],
    "createdAt": "2024-12-20T17:24:33.805Z",
    "updatedAt": "2024-12-20T18:49:18.011Z",
    "__v": 11,
    "grades": [
      {
        "studentId": "123456",
        "grade": 67
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "6765a8741e63cbb9c3ad3b1c",
    "courseId": "6762f8b6e8e5ff606e583619",
    "title": "Quiz 2",
    "description": "An MCQ quiz for chapter 2",
    "numOfQuestions": 3,
    "status": "Available",
    "easyQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "What is TCP",
        "options": [
          "A protocol",
          "A suit",
          "A model",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A protocol"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the data at network layer?",
        "options": [
          "Segment",
          "User datagrame",
          "Datagrame",
          "Frame"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Datagrame"
      }
    ],
    "mediumQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following protocols is used for email services?",
        "options": [
          "SMTP",
          "FTP",
          "HTTP",
          "IMAP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "SMTP"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a subnet mask do in a network?",
        "options": [
          "Defines the gateway",
          "Determines the host ID and network ID",
          "Specifies the MAC address",
          "Controls data speed"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Determines the host ID and network ID"
      }
    ],
    "hardQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main function of a DNS server?",
        "options": [
          "Routes traffic on a network",
          "Translates domain names to IP addresses",
          "Manages the ARP table",
          "Encrypts HTTP traffic"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Translates domain names to IP addresses"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocol is used for error reporting in IP communication?",
        "options": [
          "ICMP",
          "ARP",
          "RARP",
          "UDP"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "ICMP"
      }
    ],
    "grades": [
      {
        "studentId": "123456",
        "grade": 33
      }
    ],
    "createdAt": "2024-12-20T17:25:08.937Z",
    "updatedAt": "2024-12-20T18:49:49.143Z",
    "__v": 12
  },
  {
    "_id": "6767205227898b62a6979eca",
    "courseId": "6762f8b6e8e5ff606e583619",
    "title": "quiz 3",
    "description": "jhkjhskj ksjhkajsh khskjahd",
    "numOfQuestions": 3,
    "status": "Not available",
    "easyQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "jkshkjashdkj",
        "options": [
          "a",
          "b",
          "c",
          "d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "difficulty": 1
      }
    ],
    "mediumQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "jdlasjdask lkjdlsdjsa ljslkjsald",
        "options": [
          "a",
          "b",
          "c",
          "d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "difficulty": 3
      }
    ],
    "hardQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "djwqlj o8wuoqwue ouweoqiw",
        "options": [
          "a",
          "b",
          "c",
          "d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "difficulty": 5
      }
    ],
    "grades": [],
    "createdAt": "2024-12-21T20:08:50.505Z",
    "updatedAt": "2024-12-21T20:08:50.505Z",
    "__v": 0
  },
  {
    "_id": "676723217af68a54912e9eb2",
    "courseId": "6762f8b6e8e5ff606e583619",
    "title": "Quiz 3",
    "description": "jkjkhd khdsk kjdshksd",
    "numOfQuestions": 3,
    "status": "Available",
    "easyQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "ssadas",
        "options": [
          "a",
          "b",
          "c",
          "d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "difficulty": 1
      }
    ],
    "mediumQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "saas sasadas",
        "options": [
          "a",
          "b",
          "c",
          "s"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "s",
        "difficulty": 3
      }
    ],
    "hardQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "sassd sasasa sdsadsa",
        "options": [
          "q",
          "w",
          "e",
          "d"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "q",
        "difficulty": 5
      }
    ],
    "grades": [],
    "createdAt": "2024-12-21T20:20:49.422Z",
    "updatedAt": "2024-12-21T20:20:49.422Z",
    "__v": 0
  }
]